Guide to the Robert and Wilma Jones home movies 1952-1978
Multimedia Archives, J. Willard Marriott Library, University of Utah
Robert and Wilma Jones home movies
1952-1978
University of Utah Libraries, Special Collections Audio Visual Archives Special Collections 295 South 1500 East Salt Lake City, Utah 84112-0860 (801) 581-8864
A0638
Jones family
186 8mm films with Betacam and VHS videocassette. All film reels are 25 ft long.
The Robert and Wilma Jones home movies (1952-1978) document the Jones family's birthdays, holidays, vacations and daily life at their home in Vernal, Utah. This collection is one of the most complete home movie collections held by the Multimedia Archives and gives enormous insight into the everyday life of Utahns from the 1950s through the 1970s.
The Robert and Wilma Jones home movies (1952-1978) consist of 8mm films documenting the Jones family's birthdays, holidays, vacations and daily life at their home in Vernal, Utah. This collection is one of the most complete home movie collections held by the Multimedia Archives and gives enormous insight into the everyday life of Utahns from the 1950s through the 1970s.
The materials are arraned chronologically, except where noted.
Materials must be used on-site; no use of original material, access copies will be made available for viewing. Five business days advanced notice required. Access to parts of this collection may be restricted under provisions of state or federal law, condition of the material, or by donor.
Vernal (Utah); Home movies; City and Town Life; Moving Images; Moving images; Home movies and video
- 8mm films
  - Kid's picture, 1952; 8mm film (Reel 1)
  - Kid's picture, 1953; 8mm film (Reel 2)
  - Spring, undated; 8mm film (Reel 3)
  - Easter, 1953; 8mm film (Reel 4)
  - Peter's Point move, 1953 December; 8mm film (Reel 5)
  - Kid's parade, 1953; 8mm film (Reel 6)
  - Spring, 1953; 8mm film (Reel 7)
  - Summer: Red Canyon, 1953; 8mm film (Reel 8)
  - August, 1953; 8mm film (Reel 9)
  - Christmas, 1953; 8mm film (Reel 10)
  - Las Vegas, 1954; 8mm film (Reel 11)
  - July, 1954; 8mm film (Reel 12)
  - Mother's Day, 1954; 8mm film (Reel 13)
  - Summer-fall 1954, 8mm film (Reel 14)
  - Rosemary crawling, 1954; 8mm film (Reel 15)
  - Christmas, 1954; 8mm film (Reel 16)
  - December, 1954; 8mm film (Reel 17)
  - Christmas 1954, Equity move 1955, 1954-1955; 8mm film (Reel 18)
  - Ted's birthday, 1955; 8mm film (Reel 19)
  - Father's Day, 1955; 8mm film (Reel 20)
  - Summer, Equity move, 1955; 8mm film (Reel 21)
  - Mother's Day, Dad on horse, 1955; 8mm film (Reel 22)
  - Lawn, Bill, Nevada rig, undated; 8mm film (Reel 23)
  - November, 1955; 8mm film (Reel 24)
  - Christmas, 1955; 8mm film (Reel 25)
  - 1/2 Film, 1955; 8mm film (Reel 26)
  - April, 1956; 8mm film (Reel 27)
  - Rosemary's birthday, 1956; 8mm film (Reel 28)
  - Yellowstone National Park, 1956; 8mm film (Reel 29)
  - Yellowstone National Park, 1956; 8mm film (Reel 30)
  - Kid's day, 1956; 8mm film (Reel 31)
  - Royal George and home aerial view, 1956; 8mm film (Reel 32)
  - Jack's Canyon, 1956; 8mm film (Reel 33)
  - July, 1956; 8mm film (Reel 34)
  - Christmas, 1956; 8mm film (Reel 35)
  - Ted's birthday, 1957; 8mm film (Reel 36)
  - Rosemary's birthday, 1957; 8mm film (Reel 37)
  - Summer, 1957; 8mm film (Reel 38)
  - Summer: Hecker's, 1957; 8mm film (Reel 39)
  - Summer, 1957; 8mm film (Reel 40)
  - Bobby's 6th birthday, 1957; 8mm film (Reel 41)
  - Disneyland, 1957; 8mm film (Reel 42)
  - Wayne's horse, 1958; 8mm film (Reel 43)
  - Easter, 1958; 8mm film (Reel 44)
  - Church picnic, 1958; 8mm film (Reel 45)
  - Summer, 1958; 8mm film (Reel 46)
  - Skipper's first pups, 1958; 8mm film (Reel 47)
  - Vacation, 1958; 8mm film (Reel 48)
  - Pike's Peak, 1958; 8mm film (Reel 49)
  - Summer, Colorado marble quarry, 1958; 8mm film (Reel 50)
  - Halloween, 1958; 8mm film (Reel 51)
  - Fall, Christmas, 1958; 8mm film (Reel 52)
  - Jack's Canyon, Halloween, 1958; 8mm film (Reel 53)
  - Rosemary's birthday, 1959; 8mm film (Reel 54)
  - Father's Day, 1959; 8mm film (Reel 55)
  - Summer, 1959; 8mm film (Reel 56)
  - Salt Lake pioneers, 1959; 8mm film (Reel 57)
  - Summer, 1959; 8mm film (Reel 58)
  - Bob's birthday, 1959; 8mm film (Reel 59)
  - Pepper and Peggy, 1959; 8mm film (Reel 60)
  - Wilson Creek, 1959; 8mm film (Reel 61)
  - Christmas, 1959; 8mm film (Reel 62)
  - Conk's dance review, undated; 8mm film (Reel 63)
  - Flaming Gorge, 1960; 8mm film (Reel 64)
  - Boy Scout Jamboree: Colorado Springs, 1960; 8mm film (Reel 65)
  - Boy Scout Jamboree: Colorado Springs, 1960; 8mm film (Reel 66)
  - Rosemary's birthday, 1960; 8mm film (Reel 67)
  - Summer: Glacier National Park, 1960; 8mm film (Reel 68)
  - Summer: Glacier National Park, 1960; 8mm film (Reel 69)
  - Leaving Glacier National Park for Yellowstone National Park, 1960; 8mm film (Reel 70)
  - Yellowstone National Park, Earthquake Lake, 1960; 8mm film (Reel 71)
  - West Yellowstone, Earthquake Lake, 1960; 8mm film (Reel 72)
  - Summer: Yellowstone, home, 1960; 8mm film (Reel 73)
  - Bob's birthday, Christmas, 1960; 8mm film (Reel 74)
  - Halloween, 1960; 8mm film (Reel 75)
  - Wayne's 14th birthday, Ted's 12th birthday, 1960, 1961; 8mm film (Reel 76)
  - Ted's 12th birthday, Rosemary's 8th birthday, 1961; 8mm film (Reel 77)
  - Easter, aerial shot of house, Rosemary, 1961; 8mm film (Reel 78)
  - Spring, 1961; 8mm film (Reel 79)
  - Horse and animals, 1961; 8mm film (Reel 80)
  - Summer, 1961; 8mm film (Reel 81)
  - Bob's dad, trucks in Michigan, 1961; 8mm film (Reel 82)
  - Fall, Cisne, Dad's parents, 1961; 8mm film (Reel 83)
  - Summer, fall, Cisne, Halloween, 1961; 8mm film (Reel 84)
  - Bob's 10th birthday, Christmas, 1961; 8mm film (Reel 85)
  - Trucks, winter, kids rabbits, spring, 1961-1962; 8mm film (Reel 86)
  - Big Bob's birthday, Easter, 1962; 8mm film (Reel 87)
  - Rosemary's 9th birthday, 1962; 8mm film (Reel 88)
  - Spring, 1962; 8mm film (Reel 89)
  - Rosemary's 9th birthday, summer, Bobby's 11th birthday, 1962; 8mm film (Reel 90)
  - Summer trip to Seattle World's Fair, 1962; 8mm film (Reel 91)
  - Summer trip to Seattle World's Fair, Victoria, Canada, 1962; 8mm film (Reel 92)
  - Summer trip to Seattle World's Fair, 1962; 8mm film (Reel 93)
  - Bobby's 11th birthday, horses, 1962; 8mm film (Reel 94)
  - Bobby's 11th birthday, Christmas, 1962; 8mm film (Reel 95)
  - Christmas, Wayne's 16th birthday, Mother's 39th birthday, 1962-1963; 8mm film (Reel 96)
  - Ted's 14th birthday, 1963; 8mm film (Reel 97)
  - Easter Culver, 1963; 8mm film (Reel 98)
  - Culver Mother's Day, 1963; 8mm film (Reel 99)
  - Culver Mother's Day, 1963; 8mm film (Reel 100)
  - Culver Mother's Day, 1963; 8mm film (Reel 101)
  - Rosemary's 10th birthday, 1963; 8mm film (Reel 102)
  - Summer, Hannibal, Missouri, Fall Culver, 1963; 8mm film (Reel 103)
  - Culver Fall, 1963; 8mm film (Reel 104)
  - Bobby's birthday, 1963; 8mm film (Reel 105)
  - Bobby's birthday, 1963; 8mm film (Reel 106)
  - Halloween, 1963; 8mm film (Reel 107)
  - Summer, Gettysburg, 1964; 8mm film (Reel 108)
  - Summer, Valley Forge Jamboree, 1964; 8mm film (Reel 109)
  - Summer, 1964; 8mm film (Reel 110)
  - Summer, New York, Gettysburg, 1964; 8mm film (Reel 111)
  - Ted's birthday, 1964; 8mm film (Reel 112)
  - Thanksgiving, 1964; 8mm film (Reel 113)
  - Christmas, 1964; 8mm film (Reel 114)
  - Wayne's birthday, 1964; 8mm film (Reel 115)
  - Inagural parade for President Lyndon Johnson (LBJ), 1965; 8mm film (Reel 116)
  - Rosemary's birthday, 1965; 8mm film (Reel 117)
  - Exeter rig, Flaming Gorge, Crazy Horse, South Dakota, 1965; 8mm film (Reel 118)
  - Summer vacation, South Dakota, 1965; 8mm film (Reel 119)
  - Rosemary's 12th birthday, Bobby's 14th birthday, Grandma Bennett, 1965; 8mm film (Reel 120)
  - Fall Culver, Christmas, 1965; 8mm film (Reel 121)
  - Christmas, Bobby's 15th birthday, 1965, 1966; 8mm film (Reel 122)
  - Culver, June, Wayne's graduation, 1966; 8mm film (Reel 123)
  - Culver, June, Wayne's graduation, 1966; 8mm film (Reel 124)
  - Culver, June, Wayne's graduation, 1966; 8mm film (Reel 125)
  - Culver, June, Wayne's graduation, 1966; 8mm film (Reel 126)
  - Culver, June, Wayne's graduation, 1966; 8mm film (Reel 127)
  - Culver, June, Wayne's graduation, 1966; 8mm film (Reel 128)
  - Culver, June, Wayne's graduation, 1966; 8mm film (Reel 129)
  - Culver, June, Wayne's graduation, 1966; 8mm film (Reel 130)
  - Wayne's 20th birthday, Rosemary's 14th birthday, 1966, 1967; 8mm film (Reel 131)
  - Culver, Mother's Day, Alaska, 1967; 8mm film (Reel 132)
  - Alaska trip, 1967; 8mm film (Reel 133)
  - Alaska trip, 1967; 8mm film (Reel 134)
  - Alaska trip, 1967; 8mm film (Reel 135)
  - Alaska trip, 1967; 8mm film (Reel 136)
  - Alaska trip, 1967; 8mm film (Reel 137)
  - Alaska trip, 1967; 8mm film (Reel 138)
  - Alaska trip, 1967; 8mm film (Reel 139)
  - May, June, Culver, Ted's graduation, 1968; 8mm film (Reel 140)
  - May, June, Culver, Ted's graduation, 1968; 8mm film (Reel 141)
  - May, June, Culver, Ted's graduation, 1968; 8mm film (Reel 142)
  - May, June, Culver, Ted's graduation, 1968; 8mm film (Reel 143)
  - May, 1969; 8mm film (Reel 144)
  - May, 1970; 8mm film (Reel 145)
  - Winter, 1971; 8mm film (Reel 146)
  - February, 1971; 8mm film (Reel 147)
  - Oregon, 1977; 8mm film (Reel 148)
  - Panama Canal, 1977; 8mm film (Reel 149)
  - Panama Canal, Cartogenia, 1977; 8mm film (Reel 150)
  - South Pacific, 1977; 8mm film (Reel 151)
  - South Pacific, Australia, 1977; 8mm film (Reel 152)
  - Singapore, 1977; 8mm film (Reel 153)
  - India, Ganges, 1977; 8mm film (Reel 154)
  - Calcutta, 1977; 8mm film (Reel 155)
  - India, Suez, Cairo, 1977; 8mm film (Reel 156)
  - Egypt, Cairo, Alexander, 1977; 8mm film (Reel 157)
  - Malta, Maderia, 1977; 8mm film (Reel 158)
  - Fort Lauderdale, 1977; 8mm film (Reel 159)
  - Wayne's family, 1977; 8mm film (Reel 160)
  - Wayne's family, 1977; 8mm film (Reel 161)
  - Wayne's family, 1977; 8mm film (Reel 162)
  - North Sea, 1978; 8mm film (Reel 163)
  - Norway, 1978; 8mm film (Reel 164)
  - Norway, 1978; 8mm film (Reel 165)
  - Norway, 1978; 8mm film (Reel 166)
  - Norway, 1978; 8mm film (Reel 167)
  - Oslo, 1978; 8mm film (Reel 168)
  - Norway, 1978; 8mm film (Reel 169)
  - Denmark, 1978; 8mm film (Reel 170)
  - Amsterdam, 1978; 8mm film (Reel 171)
  - Russia, 1978; 8mm film (Reel 172)
  - Russia, 1978; 8mm film (Reel 173)
  - Russia, 1978; 8mm film (Reel 174)
  - Lenningrad, 1978; 8mm film (Reel 175)
  - Lenningrad, 1978; 8mm film (Reel 176)
  - Lenningrad, 1978; 8mm film (Reel 177)
  - Hamburg, 1978; 8mm film (Reel 178)
  - Family reunion, 1978; 8mm film (Reel 179)
  - Unknown film, undated; 8mm film (Reel 180)
  - Unknown film, undated; 8mm film (Reel 181)
  - Unknown film, undated; 8mm film (Reel 182)
  - Unknown film, undated; 8mm film (Reel 183)
  - Wayne's birthday, 1962; 8mm film (Reel 184)
  - Family birthdays, 1960s; 8mm film (Reel 185)
  - Family, 1960s; 8mm film (Reel 186)
- VHS and Betacam videocassette copies
  VHS and Betacam copies of all films in this collection are available for use.